<?xml version="1.0"?>
<data><item><post_title>Snorkel Expands &#x2018;Kickstart&#x2019; Finance Program In Europe</post_title><ID>8679</ID><post_content>&lt;p&gt;Following initial success in the U.K., Snorkel is pleased to announce that it has expanded its &#x2018;Kickstart&#x2019; finance program to customers in France and Poland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Designed to help businesses affected by the COVID-19 pandemic, the Kickstart program helps customers to get the equipment they need today, while maximizing cashflow in the short to mid-term, as the economy restarts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The finance programs, which are available until 2nd July 2021, are provided by Snorkel Finance&#x2122;, and are available to qualifying customers in France and Poland. They are available on all Snorkel products, including aerial lifts, material lifts and telehandlers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Barry Nicholson of Snorkel Finance, said, &#x201C;This is a challenging time for our customers, many of whom were not prepared for the longevity of business interruption caused by the ongoing pandemic. We have specifically designed this program to help our customers continue to meet their customers&#x2019; needs while ensuring conservation of cashflow in the short to mid-term, while we work to overcome the pandemic and return to some business normality.&#x201D;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The details of the finance programs and how to apply can be found&#xA0;&lt;a href="https://www.snorkellifts.com/financing"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Finance is subject to status, and subject to change without notice.&lt;/p&gt;</post_content><post_excerpt/><post_date>2021-04-27 12:11:00</post_date><post_name>snorkel-expands-kickstart-finance-program-in-europe</post_name><post_author>admin_msk33zqs</post_author><post_status>publish</post_status><featured_image>https://snorkellifts.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/Snorkel-Expands-kickstart-Finance-Program-in-Europe.jpg</featured_image><post_format>standard</post_format><comment_status>open</comment_status><ping_status>open</ping_status><post_category>Uncategorized</post_category><post_tag/><ekit_post_views_count>2</ekit_post_views_count></item><item><post_title>An Electric Snorkel Investment For Naboen</post_title><ID>8685</ID><post_content>&lt;p&gt;Norwegian rental company, Naboen AS, recently took delivery of two&#xA0;&lt;a href="https://www.snorkellifts.com/equipment/category/Telehandlers/SR626E"&gt;Snorkel SR626E&lt;/a&gt;&#xA0;fully electric compact rough terrain telehandlers, as part of a larger order for 147 electric Snorkel lifts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The order, which was received in early 2021, includes two lithium-ion battery powered SR626E compact telehandlers, plus a mix of 145 Snorkel&#xA0;&lt;a href="https://www.snorkellifts.com/equipment/category/Mast-Lifts/Self-Propelled-Mast-Lifts/TM12"&gt;TM12&lt;/a&gt;&#xA0;self-propelled telescopic mast lifts,&#xA0;&lt;a href="https://www.snorkellifts.com/equipment/category/Scissor-Lifts/Electric-Scissor-Lifts/s3219e"&gt;S3219E&lt;/a&gt;&#xA0;electric slab scissor lifts, and&#xA0;&lt;a href="https://www.snorkellifts.com/equipment/category/Scissor-Lifts/Low-Level-Scissor-Lifts/s3006p"&gt;S3006P&lt;/a&gt;&#xA0;push-around mini scissor lifts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Snorkel SR626E is the world&#x2019;s first fully electric compact rough terrain telehandler. Powered by long-lasting, maintenance-free lithium-ion batteries, the Snorkel SR626E is completely zero emissions, yet delivers the same lifting capacity and four-wheel drive capabilities as its diesel powered equivalent. Capable of lifting up to 2,600kg, the SR626E reaches a maximum lifting height of up to 5.79m, and with its compact dimensions and high-grip, non-marking tyres can easily navigate confined spaces both inside and out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Celebrating 25 years in business in 2021, Naboen AS was founded in Stavanger, Norway in 1996. Through strategic planning and the development of a strong corporate culture, Naboen has developed an impressive presence as a leading general rental equipment provider in the Norwegian market with nine branches. In 2012, Naboen AS was named European small/medium-sized rental company of the year, and in 2018, they were named the European large rental company of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a focus on sustainability, Naboen has ISO 14001 certification, and operates a mostly electric rental fleet, with continuing focus on investing in &#x2018;green&#x2019; and zero emission products to replace those traditionally powered by fossil fuels and combustion engines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of their decision to invest in electric Snorkel lifts, Jone &#xD8;lberg, Business Development &amp;amp; Fleet Management at Naboen, said, &#x201C;While it has been possible to purchase small electric mobile elevating work platforms for many years, we were very interested to see the launch of the first fully electric telehandler and took the opportunity to become one of the first rental companies to offer these units to our customers. Often used in confined spaces, the zero emissions, lower noise and zero dust generation of the Snorkel SR626E will certainly be appreciated on many jobsites, in addition to the environmental benefits.&#x201D;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Matthew Elvin, CEO, Xtreme Manufacturing &amp;amp; Snorkel, said, &#x201C;It is great to see Naboen investing in electric telehandlers, and we thank them for this most recent order. Naboen are one of the leaders in terms of their environmental commitments and we are very pleased to be able to play our part by supplying electric alternatives to traditional diesel products, which still deliver the performance their customers expect.&#x201D;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This order was placed with Henrik Skibsted, Territory Manager for Scandinavia and The Baltics for Snorkel, and has been immediately deployed into their rental fleet upon delivery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information on Naboen AS, please visit&#xA0;&lt;a href="http://www.naboen.no/"&gt;www.naboen.no&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</post_content><post_excerpt/><post_date>2021-04-08 12:14:00</post_date><post_name>an-electric-snorkel-investment-for-naboen</post_name><post_author>admin_msk33zqs</post_author><post_status>publish</post_status><featured_image>https://snorkellifts.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/A-Snorkel-SR626E-Electric-Telehandler-at-Naboen-2.jpg</featured_image><post_format>standard</post_format><comment_status>open</comment_status><ping_status>open</ping_status><post_category>Uncategorized</post_category><post_tag/><ekit_post_views_count>2</ekit_post_views_count></item><item><post_title>Ahern International Expands With Danish Acquisition</post_title><ID>8697</ID><post_content>&lt;p&gt;Ahern International, the global distribution network owned by Don F. Ahern, is pleased to announce its expansion into Denmark with the acquisition of KH Lift ApS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a deal completed earlier today, the distribution division acquired the major business activities of well-established Danish distribution business, KH Lift ApS, owned by Karsten Haahr. A new entity, Ahern Denmark A/S, has been established and will take over the ongoing equipment sales, service and spare parts business with immediate effect, for leading brands including Snorkel&#x2122;. The existing KH Lift team will transition to Ahern Denmark and will operate from the current KH Lift facility in Vejle, Denmark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Karsten Haahr, founder and long-term owner of KH Lift ApS, will continue to operate the business with a focus on the sale of used equipment, as well as sales of new Instant scaffolding and Sumner material lifts, from its new headquarters in Lunderskov, Denmark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ahern Denmark A/S, led by Henrik Skibsted, will commence the take-over of the existing business operations immediately, and plans to officially launch on 1st May 2021. Henrik is currently the territory manager for Snorkel for Scandinavia and The Baltics, and will retain those responsibilities whilst also leading the Ahern Denmark business.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Matthew Elvin, CEO, Xtreme Manufacturing &amp;amp; Snorkel, and with responsibility for the Ahern International distribution network, said, &#x201C;We are very pleased to be acquiring KH Lift ApS who have been a high performing independent distributor for Snorkel for many years. It gives us great pleasure to be able to support Karsten with the next step in his journey, as well as bring a motivated and experienced team on board who have had great success in the Danish market to date.&#x201D;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#x201C;I wish Karsten the very best for the future, and look forward to building upon the solid foundations that are already in place.&#x201D;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Karsten Haahr, added, &#x201C;I am very grateful to Don, Matthew, Henrik and the Ahern International business for this opportunity and I am confident that they are the right choice to continue and expand our existing operations in Denmark. I wish them much success.&#x201D;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ahern Denmark is currently recruiting for a number of newly-created roles in preparation for the official launch in May. Interested parties can find details at&#xA0;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.aherndenmark.dk/"&gt;www.aherndenmark.dk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA0;or contact Henrik Skibsted at&#xA0;&lt;strong&gt;+45 50 53 85 22&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA0;or e-mail&#xA0;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:henrik.skibsted@aherndenmark.dk"&gt;henrik.skibsted@aherndenmark.dk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</post_content><post_excerpt/><post_date>2021-03-31 12:17:00</post_date><post_name>ahern-international-expands-with-danish-acquisition</post_name><post_author>admin_msk33zqs</post_author><post_status>publish</post_status><featured_image>https://snorkellifts.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/Ahern-Denmark.jpg</featured_image><post_format>standard</post_format><comment_status>open</comment_status><ping_status>open</ping_status><post_category>Uncategorized</post_category><post_tag/><ekit_post_views_count>2</ekit_post_views_count></item><item><post_title>Snorkel Europe Achieves ISO 14001 &amp;amp; ISO 50001 Certification</post_title><ID>8703</ID><post_content>&lt;p&gt;At its manufacturing facility in the U.K., Snorkel Europe Limited is proud to announce that it has achieved two new ISO certifications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The company, which has held ISO 9001 certification for Quality Management Systems for 16 years, achieved ISO 14001 Environmental Management &amp;amp; ISO 50001 Energy Management in 2020. Designed as frameworks which drive continuous improvement, ISO 14001 and ISO 50001 help companies to minimize their impact on the environment, conserve resources and ensure environmental regulation compliance, while ultimately improving the bottom line through the elimination of waste.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scope of the ISO certification currently relates to all actions carried out on the Snorkel manufacturing site in Washington, Tyne and Wear, but the company plans to expand this scope to include the supply chain once all on-site improvements have been completed. An onsite employee Energy &amp;amp; Environment committee involving team members from all departments supported the ISO certification process, and are leading the company to meet its 2021 goal of a 5% energy usage and waste reduction at the plant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;John Gill, Chief Manufacturing Officer at Snorkel, said, &#x201C;I am incredibly proud of the efforts of the team at Snorkel Europe in achieving ISO 14001 and 50001 certifications. It is a journey that we are taking together, and it is really rewarding to see the continued improvements across the business that come as a result of the many small steps we take each day in reducing waste.&#x201D;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#x201C;The changes that we have made as part of this process range from large investments, such as new energy efficient lighting in the factory and the development of lithium-ion battery powered equipment, to improved waste segregation.&#x201D;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information on sustainability at Snorkel, visit&#xA0;&lt;a href="https://www.snorkellifts.com/About-Us#sustainability"&gt;https://www.snorkellifts.com/About-Us#sustainability&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</post_content><post_excerpt/><post_date>2021-03-30 12:20:00</post_date><post_name>snorkel-europe-achieves-iso-14001-iso-50001-certification</post_name><post_author>admin_msk33zqs</post_author><post_status>publish</post_status><featured_image>https://snorkellifts.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/Snorkel-Europe-ISO-Certification.jpg</featured_image><post_format>standard</post_format><comment_status>open</comment_status><ping_status>open</ping_status><post_category>Uncategorized</post_category><post_tag/><ekit_post_views_count>2</ekit_post_views_count></item><item><post_title>Snorkel S3019e Wins Prestigious Iapa Award</post_title><ID>8709</ID><post_content>&lt;p&gt;Snorkel is very proud to announce that its&#xA0;&lt;a href="https://www.snorkellifts.com/equipment/category/Scissor-Lifts/Electric-Scissor-Lifts/s3019e"&gt;S3019E&lt;/a&gt;&#xA0;electric scissor lift has been named the Product of the Year &#x2013; Scissor Lifts and Vertical Mast Platforms in the annual International Awards for Powered Access (IAPAs).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jointly organized by Access International and IPAF, the IAPAs celebrate excellence in the powered access industry. Originally planned to take place as an in-person event in London in April 2020, the IAPA&#x2019;s were postponed as a result of the covid-19 pandemic, and took place virtually March 18th, 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The virtual award ceremony and IPAF summit was watched by more than 1,000 industry professionals from more than 70 countries, who saw 12 IAPA award winners announced. The Snorkel S3019E was named the winner of the Product of the Year &#x2013; Scissor Lifts and Vertical Mast Platforms, in a highly competitive category with six shortlisted entries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Snorkel CEO, Matthew Elvin accepted the award on behalf of the company. The panel of judges chose the Snorkel S3019E as the winner of this category in appreciation of its sunken scissor stack, which delivers a lower stowed height, which leads to greater safety margins, safer loading and unloading, towing and entry and exit of the platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information on the IAPA&#x2019;s, please visit&#xA0;&lt;a href="http://www.iapa-summit.info/"&gt;www.iapa-summit.info&lt;/a&gt;. The 2022 event is scheduled to take place in London, England as an in person event.&lt;/p&gt;</post_content><post_excerpt/><post_date>2021-03-29 12:23:00</post_date><post_name>snorkel-s3019e-wins-prestigious-iapa-award</post_name><post_author>admin_msk33zqs</post_author><post_status>publish</post_status><featured_image>https://snorkellifts.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/S3019E-IAPA.jpg</featured_image><post_format>standard</post_format><comment_status>open</comment_status><ping_status>open</ping_status><post_category>Uncategorized</post_category><post_tag/><ekit_post_views_count>2</ekit_post_views_count></item><item><post_title>JOFEMESA Reaches Higher With Thirty Snorkel Lifts</post_title><ID>8715</ID><post_content>&lt;p&gt;Spanish machinery rental company, JOFEMESA, has expanded its mobile elevating work platform fleet with the additional of thirty mid-size Snorkel lifts from Ahern Iberica.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the leading rental companies in Spain, JOFEMESA operates a fleet of more than 4,000 units, including more than 1,300 MEWPs. Founded in 1987, JOFEMESA has a strong presence in the south east of Spain, with branches in Madrid, Valencia, Alicante, Castell&#xF3;n, Asturias and M&#xE1;laga.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As part of continued investment, JOFEMESA recently took delivery of thirty mid-size Snorkel scissor lifts and boom lifts. The order, handed over by Ahern Iberica Managing Director, Enrique Garcia, included eight&#xA0;&lt;a href="https://www.snorkellifts.com/equipment/category/Scissor-Lifts/Rough-Terrain-Scissor-Lifts/S3370RT"&gt;S3370RT&lt;/a&gt;&#xA0;and eight&#xA0;&lt;a href="https://www.snorkellifts.com/equipment/category/Scissor-Lifts/Rough-Terrain-Scissor-Lifts/S3970RT"&gt;S3970RT&lt;/a&gt;&#xA0;compact rough terrain scissor lifts; eight&#xA0;&lt;a href="https://www.snorkellifts.com/equipment/category/Boom-Lifts/Articulated-Boom-Lifts/A46JRT"&gt;A46JRT&lt;/a&gt;&#xA0;and three A62JRT diesel rough terrain articulated boom lifts; and three&#xA0;&lt;a href="https://www.snorkellifts.com/equipment/category/Boom-Lifts/Electric-Boom-Lifts/A38E"&gt;A38E&lt;/a&gt;&#xA0;electric articulated boom lifts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#x201C;We are very pleased to expand our fleet with this latest delivery of Snorkel lifts,&#x201D; said JOFEMESA CEO, Joaqu&#xED;n Fern&#xE1;ndez.&#xA0;&#x201C;It has been great to work on this order with Enrique and the Ahern Iberica team. Our businesses share similar values and both have an unwavering commitment to customer support in our DNA.&#x201D;&#xA0;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enrique Garcia, added,&#xA0;&#x201C;JOFEMESA is a leading name in the Spanish rental industry, and we are really proud to be chosen as the supplier for this latest fleet investment. I appreciate the trust that Joaqu&#xED;n has placed in myself and Ahern Iberica, and we look forward to working together in future.&#x201D;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information on JOFEMESA, please visit&#xA0;&lt;a href="http://www.jofemesa.com/"&gt;www.jofemesa.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</post_content><post_excerpt/><post_date>2021-03-25 12:25:00</post_date><post_name>jofemesa-reaches-higher-with-thirty-snorkel-lifts</post_name><post_author>admin_msk33zqs</post_author><post_status>publish</post_status><featured_image>https://snorkellifts.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/Snorkel-Booms-and-Scissors-at-JOFEMESA-Ready-to-rent-cropped.jpg</featured_image><post_format>standard</post_format><comment_status>open</comment_status><ping_status>open</ping_status><post_category>Uncategorized</post_category><post_tag/><ekit_post_views_count>2</ekit_post_views_count></item><item><post_title>Bi-Energy For Banner Plant</post_title><ID>8721</ID><post_content>&lt;p&gt;Banner Plant is continuing to grow its fleet with more Snorkel scissor lifts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four bi-energy compact rough terrain scissor lifts, built in the UK, were recently delivered to Banner Plant&#x2019;s Rotherham depot. Snorkel UK&#x2019;s Area Sales Manager, Jon Plaskitt handed over two Snorkel S3370BE and two Snorkel S3970BE scissor lifts to Banner Plant depot manager, Phil James, and provided familiarization training.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Available on all Snorkel narrow and compact rough terrain scissor lifts, Snorkel&#x2019;s innovative bi-energy power solution delivers the ultimate in jobsite and hire flexibility. The lift can be operated using its powerful combustion engine for outdoor activities, or be easily switched to DC battery power for quiet, zero emission electric performance for use indoors or in low emission zones. The lifts come equipped as standard with high grip, non-marking tyres to perform in all environments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Snorkel S3370BE reaches a maximum working height of 12m and can lift a maximum capacity of up to 450kg. The larger S3970BE can lift a platform capacity of 350kg to a maximum working height of up to 13.8m. Both scissor lifts measure 1.8m wide, and come with a 1.2m roll-out deck extension to maximize the working area, and have impressive four-wheel drive capabilities. Four hydraulic outriggers with automatic levelling come as standard, and benefit from Snorkel&#x2019;s innovative outrigger leg design, where the cylinder is inverted to protect the rod from damage when extended.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of the recent delivery, Phil James said, &#x201C;The bi-energy power solution from Snorkel is a great option as it can be used in many more applications than a standard diesel compact rough terrain scissor lift, ultimately increasing utilization opportunities.&#x201D;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#x201C;This can either mean that a construction customer may keep the lift on hire for longer, using it on the jobsite from start to finish &#x2013; on outdoors tasks initially, and then indoors for the final fit-out stages, or it could mean that we benefit from additional hire possibilities, such as in sensitive environments or low emission zones where the use of a combustion engine may be prohibited.&#x201D;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Banner Plant operates hire centres in Dronfield, Chesterfield, Derby, Leeds, Leicester, Rotherham and Ossett, and is headquartered in Dronfield on the outskirts of Sheffield. They offer a wide range of products and services for hire and sale, including plant, powered access, big air, power tools, accommodation and serviced toilets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gary Crofts, Sales &amp;amp; Operations Director at Banner Plant added, &#x201C;Compact rough terrain scissor lifts are a popular choice for our hire customers, but we take pride in offering other variants, such as these bi-energy models, which can increase productivity or versatility in certain applications. These lifts are in addition to our already extensive fleet offering of low emission solutions that are available to our customers.&#x201D;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The four bi-energy scissor lifts were built at Snorkel&#x2019;s manufacturing facility in North East England, and feature Snorkel&#x2019;s dual-coat powder paint finish and are backed by a two-year parts and labour and five-year structural warranty as standard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#x201C;Once again, we thank Banner Plant for their continued investment in Snorkel lifts.&#x201D; said Andrew Fishburn, managing director of Snorkel UK. &#x201C;These bi-energy compact rough terrain scissor lifts are really an excellent choice for hire companies, and help to meet increasing emissions and noise regulations in certain areas and applications. Special thanks to Phil, Gary and the team. We&#x2019;re sure the bi-energy models will be a big hit at the Rotherham branch.&#x201D;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information on Banner Plant, please visit&#xA0;&lt;a href="http://www.bannerplant.co.uk/"&gt;www.bannerplant.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</post_content><post_excerpt/><post_date>2021-03-16 12:28:00</post_date><post_name>bi-energy-for-banner-plant</post_name><post_author>admin_msk33zqs</post_author><post_status>publish</post_status><featured_image>https://snorkellifts.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/Phil-James-Depot-Manager-Receives-Four-Snorkel-Bi-Energy-Scissor-Lifts.jpg</featured_image><post_format>standard</post_format><comment_status>open</comment_status><ping_status>open</ping_status><post_category>Uncategorized</post_category><post_tag/><ekit_post_views_count>2</ekit_post_views_count></item><item><post_title>First Snorkel Scissors For FTH Hire</post_title><ID>8728</ID><post_content>&lt;p&gt;FTH Hire Group have made their first investment in Snorkel&#x2122; lifts, with their recent order of ten Snorkel scissors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mixed delivery included two Snorkel&#xA0;&lt;a href="https://www.snorkellifts.com/equipment/category/Scissor-Lifts/Electric-Scissor-Lifts/S3219E"&gt;S3219E&lt;/a&gt;, four&#xA0;&lt;a href="https://www.snorkellifts.com/equipment/category/Scissor-Lifts/Electric-Scissor-Lifts/S3226E"&gt;S3226E&lt;/a&gt;&#xA0;and two&#xA0;&lt;a href="https://www.snorkellifts.com/equipment/category/Scissor-Lifts/Electric-Scissor-Lifts/S4732E"&gt;S4732E&lt;/a&gt;&#xA0;electric scissor lifts, plus two Snorkel&#xA0;&lt;a href="https://www.snorkellifts.com/equipment/category/Scissor-Lifts/Rough-Terrain-Scissor-Lifts/S3370RT"&gt;S3370RT&lt;/a&gt;&#xA0;compact rough terrain scissor lifts. Delivered in mid-February to the Farnham depot, Snorkel UK Area Sales Manager, Scott Holtby handed over the lifts and provided machine familiarization training to the FTH Hire team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FTH Hire group is a family-owned business, with more than 40 years&#x2019; experience in supplying local contractors, builders, landscapers, and craftsmen, as well as the general public, with plant and tool hire services. They operate a fleet of more than 4,000 items, including drills, sanders, cement mixers and mowers, to larger plant, including excavators, dump trucks, track chippers, as well as boom and scissor lifts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Headquartered in Farnborough, FTH Hire has six hire hubs located across Surrey, Hampshire, Berkshire and Kent serving the southeast counties of the UK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#x201C;We are committed to supplying quality equipment,&#x201D; said Peter Marsh, Director at FTH Hire Group. &#x201C;We are constantly replacing our fleet to ensure that our customers are hiring the latest equipment, which is modern, efficient and reliable.&#x201D;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#xA0;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#x201C;To meet growing demand for lifting equipment, we are very pleased to expand our fleet of scissor lifts with this recent delivery, and to take the first step with Snorkel. We were impressed by the robust build quality of the Snorkel products, the excellent paint finish which will keep the lifts looking fresher for longer, and the fact that they are assembled right here in the UK.&#x201D;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrew Fishburn, Managing Director, Snorkel UK, added, &#x201C;FTH Hire manage a large and varied fleet of equipment, so it is important to them that the equipment they purchase is very reliable and robust. We are delighted that FTH Hire chose to award Snorkel with this order, and thank them for the trust placed in our products and our team. We are confident that these scissor lifts will exceed their expectations, and we hope to become a valued long-term partner.&#x201D;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#xA0;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information on FTH Hire Group, please visit&#xA0;&lt;a href="http://www.fthhiregroup.co.uk/"&gt;www.fthhiregroup.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</post_content><post_excerpt/><post_date>2021-03-11 12:33:00</post_date><post_name>first-snorkel-scissors-for-fth-hire</post_name><post_author>admin_msk33zqs</post_author><post_status>publish</post_status><featured_image>https://snorkellifts.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/The-Snorkel-Scissor-Lifts-Delivered-to-FTH-Hires-Farnham-Depot.jpg</featured_image><post_format>standard</post_format><comment_status>open</comment_status><ping_status>open</ping_status><post_category>Uncategorized</post_category><post_tag/><ekit_post_views_count>3</ekit_post_views_count></item><item><post_title>PB Chooses Snorkel</post_title><ID>8734</ID><post_content/><post_excerpt/><post_date>2021-02-25 12:37:00</post_date><post_name>pb-chooses-snorkel</post_name><post_author>admin_msk33zqs</post_author><post_status>publish</post_status><featured_image>https://snorkellifts.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/PB-Machine-Tech-Managing-Director-Lily-Holmes-receives-the-Snorkel-A38E-from-Sean-Hopkins-Field-Sales-Representative-Ahern-Ireland-cropped.jpg</featured_image><post_format>standard</post_format><comment_status>open</comment_status><ping_status>open</ping_status><post_category>Uncategorized</post_category><post_tag/><ekit_post_views_count>1</ekit_post_views_count></item></data>
